let questions = [
  {
    question: '<b>Finish this statement:</b> In javascript, the <code>==</code> operator differs from the <code>=</code> operator in that  #blank.',
    options: [
      'the <code>==</code> operator compares values while <code>=</code> assigns them',
      'the <code>==</code> operator assigns values while <code>=</code> compares them',
      'the <code>==</code> operator assigns values globally while <code>=</code> assigns them locally',
      'the <code>==</code> operator assigns values locally while <code>=</code> assigns them globally',
    ],
    answer: 'the <code>==</code> operator compares values while <code>=</code> assigns them'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these statements initailize an empty array?',
    options: [
      '<code>var array = Array();</code>',
      '<code>var array = [];</code>',
      '<code>var array = \'\'.split(\'\');</code>',
      'All of the above'
    ],
    answer: 'All of the above'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does the DRY principle in software development stand for?',
    options: [
      'Don\'t Repeat Yourself',
      'Dump, Resolve, Yank',
      'Do Redundent Yardage'
    ],
    answer: 'Don\'t Repeat Yourself'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following methods of the String object splits a string into an array of strings based on a given delimiter?',
    options: [
      '<code>split();</code>',
      '<code>slice();</code>',
      '<code>replace();</code>',
      '<code>search();</code>'
    ],
    answer: '<code>split();</code>'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these are valid methods changing the content of an html element with the attribute <code>id="demo"</code> in Javascript?',
    options: [
      '<code>document.getElementById("demo").innerHTML = "Hello World!";</code>',
      '<code>#demo.innerHTML = "Hello World!";</code>',
      '<code>document.getElement("demo").innerHTML = "Hello World!";</code>'
    ],
    answer: '<code>document.getElementById("demo").innerHTML = "Hello World!";</code>'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where are valid locations for the <code>&lt;script&gt;</code> tag in an html file?',
    options: [
      'The <code>&lt;body&gt;</code> section',
      'The <code>&lt;head&gt;</code> section',
      'All of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'All of the above'
  },
  {
    question: 'In Javascript, what\'s the correct way to write an IF statement that checks whether some value, <code>i</code>, is NOT equal to 3?',
    options: [
      '<code>if i <> 3</code>',
      '<code>if i != 3 then</code>',
      '<code>if (i <> 3)</code>',
      '<code>if (i != 3)</code>'
    ],
    answer: '<code>if (i != 3)</code>'
  },
  {
    question: '<b>True or False:</b> JavaScript is the same as Java.',
    options: [
      'True',
      'False'
    ],
    answer: 'False'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these statements would give information about what kind of browser you\'re using?',
    options: [
      '<code>browser.name</code>',
      '<code>navigator.appVersion</code>',
      '<code>client.navName</code>'
    ],
    answer: '<code>navigator.appVersion</code>'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?',
    options: [
      '<code>oninput</code>',
      '<code>onchange</code>',
      '<code>onmouseover</code>',
      '<code>onclick</code>'
    ],
    answer: '<code>onclick</code>'
  },
]